Aviral Yadav

Penetration Tester

Working Experience of 6 months as Penetration Tester and 1 year as Web Developer. Highly Passionate for Cyber security, A forever Security Researcher and Enthusiasm. Skilled in Linux, Shell Coding, Penetration Testing, Web Exploits, Red Teaming. Strong engineering Fundamentals with a Bachelor of Technology focused in Computer Science.

Education

2016-2020	Bansal I.E.T Lucknow, Utter Pradesh
	Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science & Engineering
	Relevant Coursework: Risk Analysis, Security Threats, Access Control
2015	Gopal S.V.M. Raebareli, Utter Pradesh
	Intermediate , Relevant Coursework :- DBMS,C++
2015	Shanshiksha – Run by IIT-kanpur Former HOD-CSE
	Tranning for C++, Robotics
2013	Gopal S.V.M, Raebareli , Utter Pradesh

High School, Relevant Coursework:- Clang, WebDev Project (JavaScript)

Experience

Cyber Security Analyst

Garuda Cyber Ops Pvt. Ltd. (May 2020 - Current)

- * Work with clients to determine their requirements from the test.
- * Plan and create penetration methods, scripts and tests.
- * Carry out remote testing of a client's network or onsite testing.

Accomplishments

	Website Development
2017-2019	www.sanjumakeupstudio.online
2019-2020	www.divyapublicshool.in
2019-2020	Garuda IDS

Awards

2014	National Level Science Innovation Fair 2014, Silver Medal
	Using Robotics and Unconventional Vehicles
2013	State Level Science Innovation Fair 2013, Gold Medal

Hackathon & CTFs

2018	TechKriti – 2018, 4th Rank, IIT-Kanpur CTF Challange
2019	TechKriti – 2019, 2 nd Rank, IIT-kanpur CTF Challange

Projects

2019-2020	IDS – Garun
2019	An Advanced Anomaly Based IDS for Linux Kernel using ANN Axicom Reminder Application, Python – Flask Application

Certifications

Linux Administration: Nikhat Technologies

Personal Info

Phone
+91 8318016039
E-mail
blackhatal@gmail.com
Linked in
aviral-yadav-04293615b
WebSite
www.aviralyadav.online
Address
Sector 64,Fortise Hospital,

Noida, Utter Pradesh

Skills

Linux

Python Scripting

Web Application Security

•

Secure Software Development

Penetration Testing

Intrusion Detection

Languages

Hindi (India)

Native Proficiency

English

Professional Working Proficiency

Tools

BurpSuit, Nessus, Splunk

Metasploit, Nmap, WireShark

Kali/BlackArch Linux

Development

Python-Django, C++

JavaScript, PHP, BASH